Do you like to play board games?
Hi, my name is Dean Hale and I'm going to teach you how to get out of jail in Monopoly.
Getting in to jail happens when you roll a two of a kind three times.
How do you get out?
There's three ways to do that.
You can pay money, you can roll three times, or you can simply roll a double.
That's rolling two sixes, two fives and so on.
Why is it important to get out of jail?
Well you don't want to be in jail while other people are buying up property and making all the money.
You want to get out of jail so you can start playing Monopoly yourself.
So you would take the dice and you would just simply roll them, if you didn't get a double on your first roll, you would wait until your turn comes around again, you'd pick them up and you'd throw again.
You get two more tries, actually one more try to roll a double and then you can get out of jail.
If not, on the third try, after you do that you would get out the time after that.
Getting out of jail is important because you want to be able to buy a property or maybe you're running low on money and you don't want to land on somebody's property that's right after the jail, so you might want to stay in jail for a while.
Rolling the dice might be the best way to do that.
See if I'm in, I'm out of jail, two sixes.
My name is Dean Hale, have fun playing Monopoly.